Man missing on Tier 2 Cell 245.
Dufresne.
Get your ass out here, boy. You're holding up the show.
Don't make me come down there. I'll thump your skull for you.
Damn it, Dufresne, you're putting me behind! I got a schedule to keep.
You'd better be sick or dead in there, I shit you not! You hear me?
Oh my holy God.
I want every man on this block questioned.
Start with that friend of his.
Who?
Him!
Open 237.
What do you mean, he just wasn't here? Don't say that to me, Haig.
Don't say that to me again.
But, sir, he wasn't.
I can see that, Haig! You think I'm blind? Is that what your're saying?
Am I blind, Haig?
No, sir.
What about you? Are you blind? Tell me what this is.
Last night's count.
You see Dufresne's name there? I sure do. See? Right here. Dufresne.
He was in his cell at lights out. It stands to reason he'd still be here in the morning.
I want him found. Not tomorrow, not after breakfast. Now!
Yes, sir!
Let's go, let's go! Move your butts! Move it!
Stand.
Well?
Well, what?
I see you two all the time. You're thick as thieves, you are.
He must have said something.
No, sir, Warden. Not a word.
Lord, it's a miracle!
A man up and vanished like a fart in the wind. Nothing left but...
some damn rocks on a windowsill. And that cupcake on the wall.
Let's ask her. Maybe she knows. What say there, Fuzzy Britches?
Feel like talking? Ah.. I guess not. Why should she be any different?
This is a conspiracy. That's what this is. One big... damn conspiracy!
And everyone's in on it! Including her!
In 1966, Andy Dufresne escaped from Shawshank Prison.
All they found of him was a muddy set of prison clothes, a bar soap,
and an old rock hammer damn near worn down to the nub.
I remember thinking it would take a man 600 years to tunnel the wall with it.
Only Andy did it in less than 20.